# **Anthony Bandolon**

#### www.linkedin.com/in/abandolon

Work Visa: Germany - 2023 ■ www.github.com/Abandolon

Fullstack developer with 10 + years in Travel & Tourism Management. Energetic, professional self-starter with proven success developing multi-generational teams up to 20 people. Having a passion to identify opportunities for personal growth and develop individualized plans for improvement. In-depth knowledge of business operations, including budgeting, client services and performance analysis.

## **Core competencies include:**

Dynamic Team Management Creating in depth Reporting Automation Customer Relationship Management Proactive Problem Solving Goal Setting & Performance Tracking

## **Technical Proficiency:**

Ruby on Rails ■ APIs ■ SQL ■ HTML / CSS ■ ES6 Javascript ■ Wireframes & Prototyping UI design ■ Test driven development Git & Github ■ Amadeus GDS Airline Systems Hotel PMS Systems (Opera, Synxis, etc.)

## **Selected Professional Experience**

#### **Booking.com Germany** ■ **Berlin** ■ **Germany**

#### Partner Service Team Leader - 03/2017 - 03/2019

- Conducting regular 1:1 sessions with the team members to understand them better and also help them understand what they are trying to achieve and how.
- Familiarize the team with the customer needs, specifications, design targets, the development process, design standards, techniques and tools to support task performance.

#### **Europe Express** ■ **Bothell, WA** ■ **USA**

#### **Inside Sales Supervisor -** 03/2013 - 03/2016

- Setting and meeting performance targets for speed, efficiency, sales leads and quality.
- Supervise all agents' daily activity.
- Actively participated in the selection, training and ongoing coaching of new colleagues.

### Silver Reef Hotel Casino Spa ■ Ferndale, WA ■ USA

#### Client Relationship Manager - 07/2006 - 07/2012

- Responded to guests' queries and dealt with escalated complaints.
- Hire, train, and supervise employees; maintain open communication, provide feedback on performance, and motivate the team to excel in each area of guest service with an emphasis on total quality.
- Maximize occupancy, revenue and average rate.

# **Programming Projects**

#### GO!Rilla - https://www.gorilla-go.com

A progressive web app built in 2 weeks with a team of 4 developers.

I was responsible for the interactive Map feature with dynamic markers, overseeing the user journey, finalizing the booking process, and creating the customized CSS checkbox filter found on the "Select Your Style" page.

#### <u>AirPets</u> - https://air-pets.herokuapp.com/

Le Wagon Project - over the course of 5 days, my team of 3 developers created this MVP. This project allows pet owners to "rent" out their pets for the day.

My contributions: Installed Map Feature, overall design, created concept, managed overall Git workflow.

#### Mister Cocktail - https://mister-anthony-cocktails.herokuapp.com/

Le Wagon Project to create functioning web application in which users can add cocktails by uploading photos, selecting from a preset list of ingredients and their quantities.

### **Education**

#### Le Wagon ■ Berlin ■ Germany

### Fullstack Web Developer, Computer Programming

01/2019 - 03/2019

Attended Le Wagon Berlin (Batch #232). Le Wagon has been recognized as the best Fullstack Programming Bootcamp for the 3rd year in the row according to switchup.org.

9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails. Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of a platform which connects new gym goers with experienced people who are willing to assist.